let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which statement is used to stop a loop in Java?",
        answer: "break",
        options: [
            "stop",
            "exit",
            "break",
            "end"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does 'int' stand for in Java?",
        answer: "Integer",
        options: [
            "Internal",
            "Integral",
            "Integer",
            "Interactive"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of these is used to comment a single line in Java?",
        answer: "//",
        options: [
            "/*",
            "//",
            "**",
            "#"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the starting point of a Java program?",
        answer: "main method",
        options: [
            "first class",
            "main method",
            "main class",
            "Java file"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What do you use to create a new object in Java?",
        answer: "new",
        options: [
            "create",
            "new",
            "define",
            "build"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which keyword is used to create a variable in Java?",
        answer: "None of the above",
        options: [
            "var",
            "let",
            "create",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of these is a loop in Java?",
        answer: "for",
        options: [
            "loop",
            "repeat",
            "for",
            "do"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How do you start writing an if statement in Java?",
        answer: "if",
        options: [
            "if",
            "check",
            "test",
            "condition"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which symbol is used to denote an array in Java?",
        answer: "[]",
        options: [
            "()",
            "{}",
            "<>",
            "[]"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of these is not a valid Java data type?",
        answer: "smallint",
        options: [
            "int",
            "boolean",
            "double",
            "smallint"
        ]
    },

];
